hooqy.com 2010-05-22

# Privacy Policy

Hooqy Media is committed to protecting the privacy of all Internet users, Websites, and Advertisers. This Privacy Policy statement explains how Hooqy Media operates to protect your privacy.

Please note that Hooqy Media may find it necessary, or be legally obligated, to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected prior to the effective date of the policy change. Hooqy Media reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without notice by posting of such modification herein. Members (as defined below) and visitors should review this Privacy Policy periodically to note any changes that may have occurred. A Member (“Member”) is a corporation, other legal entity, or adult person that has applied to Hooqy Media, and has been accepted by Hooqy Media into the Network (defined below) in accordance with the terms, conditions and procedures outlined in this Website.

Hooqy Media does not collect any personal information about visitors to, or users of, this Website solely as a result of such visits or usage, other than persons or entities joining Hooqy Media’s Network (“Network”) of Websites as a Member pursuant to either a written or online contract.

When an Internet user clicks on one of Hooqy Media’s served advertisements (running throughout the Network), Hooqy Media does collect “ad delivery and reporting data” (type of browser, operating system, IP address, domain type, page(s) visited, date and time of when an Internet user has responded to an advertisement, etc.). None of the data can be linked to any individual Internet user, and therefore it cannot be used for personal identification or profiling. Hooqy Media does not collect any personally identifiable information regarding the user that clicked on the ad (e.g. name, address, social security number, e-mail address, etc.).

Some information is collected through “Cookies” as described below.

##### “Cookies”

An Internet user’s browser normally places Cookies that contain small amounts of data on the Internet user’s computer after a visit to any Website. Cookies assist Hooqy Media in tracking Internet users’ activities beginning from a Member’s Website or e-mail. If the Internet user visits or revisits an advertiser’s site directly from such Member, Hooqy Media is able to continue to track the Internet user’s activities on the advertiser’s site and reward the Member that referred the Internet user. The Cookies tell Hooqy Media nothing about the Internet user personally.

Cookies are used (1) when an advertiser’s banner image or other text is loaded on a Webpage for viewing by an Internet user, and (2) when the banner or other text is clicked by an Internet user. The function of these Cookies is to provide Hooqy Media with information solely for the purpose of paying a Member’s commissions when an Internet user clicks on a link or makes a purchase on an advertiser’s Website.

##### Member-Identifiable Data

Hooqy Media collects certain personally identifiable information from Websites and their owners wishing to join the Network. The collection of this information is a part of normal business practices. Persons and entities wishing to become Members and join the Network are asked to provide personally identifiable data through the sign up and registration process. Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, tax ID number, VAT number, etc. All personally identifiable information that Hooqy Media collects from potential and actual Members is principally intended for internal administrative needs such as accounting and invoicing.

Periodically Hooqy Media may desire to communicate with the Network of Members via e-mail newsletters or other methods to offer marketing information or other communications to assist in business related activities. In such instances Hooqy Media will access Members’ personally identifiable information. In the event that a Member wishes not to have personally identifiable information used as described in this paragraph, such Member may elect to opt-out by notifying Hooqy Media in writing or electronically at any time.

All personally identifiable data provided by individual Members will be kept in strict confidence by Hooqy Media and will be treated with the same level of care that Hooqy Media treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets; notwithstanding the foregoing, Hooqy Media may in limited instances provide personally identifiable information to a third party to assist Hooqy Media in normal and customary operational and statistical matters, or for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and payouts. Any third-party receiving such information will be required to treat it in a confidential and safeguarded manner, in accordance with industry standards and in accordance with the policies stated herein. In the event that a Member wishes not to have personally identifiable information used as described in this paragraph, such Members may elect to opt-out by notifying Hooqy Media in writing or electronically at any time.

##### Security Precautions

Hooqy Media makes every effort to maintain the security of its Network, business operations and any and all data collected. Any data that is stored on Hooqy Media’s servers are treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Hooqy Media has a strict internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees or third parties that have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering Hooqy Media’s products and services; notwithstanding any other provision herein, information may be disclosed:

  * to government agencies or officials or other third parties if Hooqy Media believes such disclosure to be required or compelled under applicable law or regulations or legal process;
  * to government agencies or officials upon their request, even if not compelled by a subpoena or other legal process, and without any duty on Hooqy Media’s part to independently confirm that such agencies or officials are legally entitled to such disclosure;
  * to a buyer, subcontractor or agent, in the event that Hooqy Media sells or transfers ownership, operation or control of any or all of its Networks or engages any subcontractor or agent to operate any Network or provide any service related to any Network.

##### Access to Data

Hooqy Media allows Members and potential Members who have provided personally identifiable data, access to such data at any reasonable time, in order to ensure that such data is correct, and to make any changes.

##### Privacy Policy Statements of Members

Hooqy Media encourages all Websites within the Network to create privacy policy statements and provide Internet users with prominently placed access to such statements. Additionally, Hooqy Media requests that all Website publishers doing business with Hooqy Media disclose any and all information that is being collected from Internet users on their Website, including data gathered from banners and other forms of advertising being served on their Website.

##### Spam and E-mail lists

Hooqy Media does not intentionally send unsolicited e-mail messages that could be construed as spam; Members’ actions are carefully scrutinized and each Member is expected to adhere to Hooqy Media’s anti-spam policy.

##### Miscellaneous

Various state and federal regulations may apply to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. Hooqy Media is sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Hooqy Media’s Website, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children.

Hooqy Media supports and endorses the BBBOnline privacy program. For more information on the specifics of the program, please go to [www.bbbonline.com](http://www.bbbonline.com/).

* * *

##### Contacting Hooqy Media

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding Hooqy Media’s Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to [info@Hooqy.com](mailto:info@Hooqy.com) or you may send correspondence to our office through normal U.S. mail.
